[I won't work overtime today]
[本宫今天不加班]
[Episode 8]
[第八集]
Done
做完了
Then let's go home
那我们回家吧
What are you posting here
你这贴的是什么呀
Is this one
这个吗
My Little Mark Little Moon
我的小标记 小月亮
No matter how insignificant it is
就算再微不足道
Work hard too
也要努力
Make your own mark
留下自己的印记
Mr. Li
李总
Detailed team battle recruitment plan
细化的团战招聘方案
What do you think
您觉得怎么样
In such a short time
在这么短时间内
Able to make relatively mature solutions
能做出相对成熟的方案
Very nice
很不错
This plan is mainly composed of
这次方案主要由
The leader of the three groups in our center
我们中心三组的组长
Li Jiakai
李佳凯
Proposed and perfected
提出并进行完善的
It's not as good as this plan
不如这次方案
Just let him execute it
就让他来执行
Li Jiakai
李佳凯
How long has he been in the company
他来公司多久了
Li Jia Kaijin Company
李佳凯进公司
It's been five years
已经有五年了
Five years
五年的时间
People who have never had any thoughts
都没有过任何想法的人
Director Wu
吴总监
From what year did you feel
你是从哪一年觉得
What about his sudden thoughts
他变得突然有想法的呢
I hope you're only confused once in a while
我希望你只是偶尔糊涂
Go busy
去忙吧
Mr. Wu
吴总
Then Lee always agrees with me
那么李总是同意我
Have you implemented this plan
执行这个方案了吗
Mr. Wu, look
吴总 您看
This case
这案子
How to adjust it
需要怎么调整
I'm going to adjust it right away
我马上去调整
There are three types of recruitment themes in the scenario
方案中有三种招聘主题
Which one do you prefer
你倾向于哪一种
What about me personally
我个人呢
More inclined to the second
比较倾向于第二种
Of course
当然了
The third one is also good
第三种呢 也不错
What about the first
第一种呢
It also has its own advantages
也有它自己的优势
But I still want Mr. Wu
但是还是要吴总
To decide
来定夺了
In this scheme
这方案中
There are two recruitment topics in total
一共就两种招聘主题
Where did you get the third kind
你哪儿来的第三种
Look at me recently
你看我这最近啊
Staying up late too much
熬夜熬太多了
Yes, there are only two kinds
对 就两种
Good
好
Who actually made this scheme
这个方案到底是谁做的
Can anyone answer my question
谁能回答我的问题
Team Recruitment Ideas
团队招聘的想法
From our company
来自于我们公司
In small groups
以小组
Working form for units
为单位的工作形式
Is to save costs quickly
是为了迅速节约成本
Put to work
投入工作
Resulting from
而产生的
The current cycle is five months
现在的周期是五个月
Very good
很好
Now cycle
现在周期
Needs to be compressed to three months
需要压缩到三个月
It's your responsibility
由你负责
Temporarily held
暂时担任
Acting leader of three groups
三组的代理组长
As for you
至于你
Voluntarily leave now
现在主动离职
I can
我可以
I'll give you three months' salary
给你三个月的工资
As compensation
作为补偿
Others
其他人
Cooperate with He Jiaojiao's work
配合何皎皎的工作
We'll start next week
下周我们就开始行动
Mr. Wu, you, you, me
吴总 你 你 我
He Jiaojiao
何皎皎
Mr. Wu, please don't
吴总 你别
Let me explain
你听我解释
Let's go celebrate
我们去庆祝吧
It's really worth celebrating
真是值得庆祝一下
What's Komatsu doing?
小松 瞎蹦达什么呢
Don't you understand if you don't see any indecent assault
非礼勿视不懂吗
What are you talking about
你在说什么呢
I can't hear you clearly
我听不清
I said they were all crazy
我说他们都疯了
You haven't seen the world
你没见过世面
He Jiaojiao
何皎皎
You just didn't drink enough
你就是没喝够
Come, come, come, come
来来来
Drink, drink, drink
喝酒 喝酒 喝酒
You don't even call sister anymore, do you
你连姐都不叫了是吧
Sister, what sister
姐什么姐
After drinking this cup, you are brothers
喝完这杯就是兄弟
-No, no, no, I'm not drinking
-不不不 我不喝 -喝 喝
Drink, drink, drink
喝 喝 喝
Small pine nuts
小松子
These are all gifts from the emperor
这些都是皇上赏赐的
Yeah
对呀
Little master, you are going to be favored again
小主 你是又要受宠了
I'm bringing something nice
我带来个好东西
Why don't we celebrate and celebrate
咱们要不庆祝庆祝
WHAT THING
什么东西
Wine
酒啊
No, no, no, no
不行 不行 不行
I can't drink
我不会喝酒
I'll get drunk
我会喝醉的
Try it. It tastes delicious
试试嘛 很好喝的
It's delicious to drink
很好喝
Then I'll have a taste
那我尝尝
Should be fine
应该没事吧
Touch it
碰一下
One more drink, one more drink
再来一杯 再来一杯
How about it? Does it taste good
怎么样 好喝吗
Jiaojiao
皎皎
I'm sorry
对不起
I've been targeting you all the time before
之前我一直还针对你
But you can come and be our team leader
不过你能来当我们组长
I'm really happy
我是真的很开心
Never again
再也不用
Being bullied by that Li Jiakai
被那个李佳凯欺负了
That is
就是
Come
来
To Jiaojiao
对 皎皎
Me, Sister Li, I'm accurate in judging people
我啊 李姐我看人准
Look at Li Jiakai
你看那李佳凯
Don't say
别说
-Come on, come on, drink, drink, drink
-来来来 喝酒 喝酒 喝酒 -喝
Come, come, come, come
来来来
Dry dry dry
干 干 干
Cheers Cheers
干杯 干杯
That Mr. Li
那个 李总
This is all out
这都出来了
Just relax
您就放松一下吧
That's what you're talking about
这就是你说的
Make an appointment to meet with customers
约的客户见面
Isn't it Friday today
这不今天周五嘛
Tomorrow is your birthday
明天您生日
We big guys
我们大家伙
Just wanted to celebrate for you
就想给您庆祝一下
Is it not
是不是
Celebrate
庆祝一下
I'm bored, I'll go first
无聊 我先走了
Etc. etc.
等 等 等
Wait wait wait
等 等 等 等
Mr. Li, Mr. Li, wait a minute
李总 李总 等会儿
Would you like to sit down for a while
您坐会儿 坐会儿
You listen to me
您听我说
We also ordered a cake
我们还订了蛋糕呢
Would you like to eat more or less
您多少吃一点
Give some face
给点面子
Have this time
有这个时间
Why don't you delve into the business
不如好好钻研一下业务
Hurry up
赶紧上吧
The waiter
那个 服务员
Prepare to serve the cake, serve the cake
准备上蛋糕 上蛋糕
Mr. Li, please listen to me
那个 李总 您听我说
I ordered this cake for you
我给你订的这个蛋糕
You are absolutely satisfied
您绝对满意
Is a huge surprise
是一个巨大的惊喜
Must fit your advanced aesthetics
一定符合您高级的审美
Noble and elegant
高贵 典雅
It looks eye-catching
看上去让人眼前一亮
And contains
又蕴含着
Extremely full
极其饱满
And rich emotions are in it
且丰富的情感在里边
Let's all give it to Mr. Li
我们大家给李总
Can you sing a song
唱个歌好不好呀
OK OK
好 好 好
Three two one
三 二 一
♪ Say goodbye to all your worries ♪
♪跟所有的烦恼说拜拜♪
♪ Say hi hi to all the happiness ♪
♪跟所有的快乐说嗨嗨♪
♪ Darling darling ♪
♪亲爱的 亲爱♪
That on the cake on the cake
那个 上蛋糕 上蛋糕
Who is today's birthday girl
哪位是今天的寿星啊
He
他
Didn't I make it clear to you
要求我没跟你说清楚吗
European courts
欧洲宫廷
Noble, elegant and classic
高贵典雅 经典不衰
Didn't your eyes light up
你的眼前没有一亮吗
My eyes really lit up
我眼前确实一亮
Mr. Li
李总
Let me explain that
那个 听我解释
That's not what happened
不是这么回事
I arranged
我安排的
Next month's salary cut in half
下个月工资减半
Mr. Li Li
李 李总
You listen to me, you listen to me
你听我说 你听我说
By the way, I told you before
对了 之前让你了解的
Jobs in African Mining Projects
非洲挖矿的项目的岗位
Is there any news
有消息了吧
Prepare yourself
自己准备一下
Not wait, wait, wait
不是 等等等
Mr. Li Mr. Li
李总 李总
Mr. Li, listen to me
李总 你听我说
Listen to my explanation, Mr. Li
你听我解释 李总
I drink it myself
我自己喝
Don't you drink it either
你也别喝
No, I'll drink it myself
不行 我自己喝
Just drink
就喝
Give me
给我
I'll go to the bathroom first
我先上个厕所
No, what toilet
不行 上什么厕所
Come back soon
快回来
You
你
Where are you going
你要去哪儿啊
Everyone, get out of my way
都给本宫让开
You guys, I'm telling you
你们这些人 我跟你讲
Dancing is not as good as me
跳舞都没我好看
Come, come, come, come
来 来 来
Drink it and the world will fall apart
喝 喝它个天崩地裂
Sky fall and earth fall
天崩地裂
Drink
喝
Emperor
皇上
Why doesn't Komatsu drink it
小松 怎么不喝
Hurry up, drink and clink glasses
快点 喝酒 碰杯
The emperor is coming up
皇上来了
I'd like to see the emperor
我倒要看看皇上
Small pine nuts
小松子
Emperor
皇上
What's going on
怎么回事
Pretty handsome
还挺帅的
Your Majesty
皇上 这
Who made her drink so much
谁让她喝这么多酒的
Let go of her. She's my guy
放开 她是我的人
Brother, you're wrong
兄弟 你这不对了啊
There is always a first-come-first-served approach in everything
凡事总有个先来后到
I told you she was mine
我说了 她是我的人
You get out of my way
你给我让开
Did you see
看到没有
It was posted by the little beauty herself
是小美人自己贴上来的
Are you trying to flirt with me
你是不是想撩我
I'll go
我去
Little sister is quite active
小妹妹挺主动的啊
My feet
我的脚
What do you want to do to me
想对我怎么着
Dare to mess with my sister Jiaojiao
敢惹我皎皎姐
I will destroy you on behalf of the moon
我要代表月亮消灭你们
Let's take you home
走 带你回家
No, no, no, no
不行 不行 不行
No, no, no, I have to dance
不行 不行 我还要跳舞
Get her stuff
把她东西都拿上
I want to dance
我要跳舞
I want to sing
我要歌唱
Fortunately, Komatsu protected me
还好有小松护住了我
I'll never drink again
我以后再也不喝酒了
Can't drink and still drink so much
不能喝还喝这么多
Stupid to death
笨死了
Let me go
放开我
I want to drink
我要喝酒
Don't move
别动
Let me go
放开我
Let go, I want a drink
放开 我要喝酒
He Jiaojiao
何皎皎
I'm going to drink it for another three days and three nights
我要再喝它个三天三夜
Don't move
别动了
What's so noisy? It's so noisy
凶什么凶 吵死了
This feel
这个手感
So this is how it is
原来是这样的呀
He looks pretty handsome
长得还挺帅
You look like someone
你跟一个人长得好像啊
It's just as unstoppable
一样让人欲罢不能
You said you obviously had everything
你说你明明什么都有了
Why do you want to
为什么要
How many times have you approached me
几次三番地接近我呢
Isn't it
难道不是
Did you approach me first
你先接近我的吗
Obviously you will leave me
明明你就会离开我
Why do you have to
为什么还要
How many times have you given me a chance
几次三番地给我机会呢
I don't have me
我没有 我
Your heart
你这心
Is it beating for me alone
是为我一个人跳动的吗
He Jiaojiao, don't move around
何皎皎 别乱动
You don't want me anymore
你不要我了
You're in front of everyone
你当着所有人的面
Don't want me anymore
不要我了
You don't want me anymore
你不要我了
Look at me
看着我
I didn't have
我没有
You this
你这个
Cold and cold big pig's trotters
冷情冷意的大猪蹄子
Hello
喂
[Sister Jiaojiao, where are you]
[皎皎姐 你在哪儿呢]
I'm at home
我在家呀
[That's good, that's good]
[那就好 那就好]
Not you
不是你
[I'm sleeping myself]
[我自己都睡蒙了]
[By the way]
[对了]
[It seems today]
[今天好像]
[It's still Mr. Li's birthday]
[还是李总的生日]
Li Su
李溯
[Sister Jiaojiao]
[皎皎姐]
[Look at the circle of friends]
[你快看朋友圈]
[And our work group]
[还有我们的工作群]
[They need to]
[他们有必要]
[Is it so exaggerated?]
[这么夸张吗]
In the palace
在宫里
Build a good relationship with your superiors
和上级打好关系
Is very important
是非常重要的
Unexpectedly
没想到
It's so exaggerated now
现在也这么夸张
There are actually people stuck at zero points
居然还有人卡零点